- question: "Is Python case sensitive when dealing with identifiers?"
  answers:
    - "*yes"
    - "no"
    - "machine dependent"
    - "none of the mentioned"
  explanation: "Case is always significant while dealing with identifiers in python."

- question: "What is the maximum possible length of an identifier?"
  answers:
    - "31 characters"
    - "63 characters"
    - "79 characters"
    - "*none of the mentioned"
  explanation: "Identifiers can be of any length."

- question: "Which of the following is invalid?"
  answers:
    - "_a = 1"
    - "__a = 1"
    - "__str__ = 1"
    - "*none of the mentioned"
  explanation: "All the statements will execute successfully but at the cost of reduced readability."

- question: "Which of the following is an invalid variable?"
  answers:
    - "my_string_1"
    - "*1st_string"
    - "foo"
    - "_"
  explanation: "Variable names should not start with a number."

- question: "Why are local variable names beginning with an underscore discouraged?"
  answers:
    - "*they are used to indicate a private variables of a class"
    - "they confuse the interpreter"
    - "they are used to indicate global variables"
    - "they slow down execution"
  explanation: "As Python has no concept of private variables, leading underscores are used to indicate variables that must not be accessed from outside the class."

- question: "Which of the following is not a keyword?"
  answers:
    - "*eval"
    - "assert"
    - "nonlocal"
    - "pass"
  explanation: "eval can be used as a variable."

- question: "All keywords in Python are in _________"
  answers:
    - "*lower case"
    - "UPPER CASE"
    - "Capitalized"
    - "None of the mentioned"
  explanation: "True, False and None are capitalized while the others are in lower case."

- question: "Which of the following is true for variable names in Python?"
  answers:
    - "*unlimited length"
    - "all private members must have leading and trailing underscores"
    - "underscore and ampersand are the only two special characters allowed"
    - "none of the mentioned"
  explanation: "Variable names can be of any length."

- question: "Which of the following is an invalid statement?"
  answers:
    - "abc = 1,000,000"
    - "*a b c = 1000 2000 3000"
    - "a,b,c = 1000, 2000, 3000"
    - "a_b_c = 1,000,000"
  explanation: "Spaces are not allowed in variable names."

- question: "Which of the following cannot be a variable?"
  answers:
    - "__init__"
    - "*in"
    - "it"
    - "on"
  explanation: "in is a keyword."
